Guide to the Center for Women Policy Studies records, 1970-2012 and undated RL.00282
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2015-0192) 1953-2012, 29 boxes
  - Jessie Bernard Wise Women Awards, 2000-2001 (Box 194)
  - Pacific Rim Program, 2012 (Box 194)
  - Board of Directors Manual, 2011 (Box 194)
  - Women and AIDS: An Annotated Bibliography for Project Staff and Clients, July 1989 (Box 194)
  - AIDS Litigation Project, 1990 (Box 194)
  - America Living With AIDS, 1991 (Box 194)
  - CGP Intellectual Exchange, 2012 (Box 195)
  - AIDS Prevention Among Female Sexual Partners of Intravenous Drug Users, March 1989 (Box 195)
  - HIV/AIDS Prevention v.I - NIDA, 1989 (Box 195)
  - Women and Drugs: An Annotated Bibliography, December 1990 (Box 195)
  - Miscellaneous Papers on Postsecondary Education and Welfare Reform, 2004 (Box 195)
  - Post-Election Action Convening (PEAC) for Women State Legislators, 2012 (Box 195)
  - "Clipping Our Wings", December 2001 (Box 195)
  - Violence Against Women as Bias Motivated Hate Crime, 1991 (Box 195)
  - On the Cutting Edge (Box 195)
  - GRANT FUNDER FILE - Educational Foundation of America (EFA), 2008-2009 (Box 195)
  - Educational Foundation of America (EFA), 2011-2013 (Box 195)
  - Women and AIDS: An Annotated Bibliography for Project Staff and Clients, December 1989 (Box 195)
  - Assorted Items, 2005-2011 (Box 196)
  - Board Meeting, April 8, 2005 (Box 196)
  - Sample of 2010 GP Packet - Exact Contents (Box 196)
  - CWPS Newsletters, 2002-2006 (Box 196)
  - GlobalPOWER Africa, 2012 (Box 196)
  - UNDP Grant, 2012 (Box 196)
  - Pacific Rim 2012 Statement (Box 196)
  - REPORTS, 1995-2005 (Box 196)
  - Board of Directors, 2001-2006 (Box 196)
  - A Living History: 150 Years of Women's Rights, 1998 (Box 196)
  - Quest: A Feminist Quarterly, 1976-1978 (Box 196)
  - Margaret Sanger: Pioneer of Birth Control, 1969 (Box 197)
  - Generation Unbound: Drifting Into Sex and Parenthood Without Marriage, 2014 (Box 197)
  - Thinking and Rethinking U.S. History, 1988 (Box 197)
  - Womens Survival Manual: A Feminist Handbook on Separation and Divorce, 1972 (Box 197)
  - Sex Role Socialization and Sex Discrimination: A Synthesis and Critique of the Literature, October 1979 (Box 197)
  - GlobalPOWER 2009 & PDF Files Archive CDs (Box 197)
  - "Fighting for Our Lives: Women Confronting AIDS": A Video for the Center for Woman Policy Studios (Box 197)
  - Assorted Black & White Photographs/Negatives, 1965-1975 (Box 197)
  - Photographs of Leslie Wolfe, 1973-1982 (Box 197)
  - Assorted Photographs, 1982-1986 (Box 198)
  - Photographs of Think Tank on Future of Women's Movement, November 1993 (Box 198)
  - Guest Book - Reception Honoring Leslie Wolfe, January 20, 1982 (Box 198)
  - Assorted CD's, 2006-2009 (Box 198)
  - Invite: Third Annual Jessie Bernard Wise Women Awards Luncheon, October 25, 1991 (Box 198)
  - Wise Women Awards Cassettes, March 2000 (Box 198)
  - Welfare & College Option Conference Photos and Board of Directors Photo Sheet, 1997-1999 (Box 198)
  - WW Photos, 1991-1993 (Box 198)
  - WW, 1992 (Box 199)
  - FPI Class of 2003 @ Dept. of State, November 2003 (Box 199)
  - FPI, 2008 (Box 199)
  - PPI, 2009 (Box 199)
  - Untitled Photos, 2008 (Box 199)
  - WW Rolls 4-9, 1993 (Box 200)
  - WW & County Paper Think Tank, 1993 (Box 200)
  - WW Rolls 1-8, 1994 (Box 200)
  - WW, 1995 (Box 200)
  - WW, 1995 (Box 201)
  - WW Rolls 1-8, March 18,1999 (Box 201)
  - Welfare & College Option Conference, September 1999 (Box 201)
  - WW Roll 1 and Assorted Items, 2000 (Box 201)
  - WW Rolls 2-5, 2000 (Box 202)
  - WW, 2001 (Box 202)
  - Congressional Briefing on TANF, 2002 (Box 202)
  - RRH MD/VA, 2003 (Box 202)
  - FPI, 2003 (Box 202-203)
  - FPI & CO RR Exchange, 2003 (Box 203)
  - NCSL 2003 & FPI 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 203)
  - FPI, 2005 (Box 203)
  - PEAC Rolls 1-3, 2005 (Box 203)
  - FPI Rolls 1-2, 2005 (Box 203)
  - FPI Rolls 3-4, 2005 (Box 204)
  - NCSL Trafficking & Luncheon, 2005 (Box 204)
  - FPI Day Conference, 2006 (Box 204)
  - FPI Evening Dinner, 2006 (Box 204)
  - GlobalPOWER, 2005 (Box 204)
  - GlobalPOWER, 2006 (Box 204)
  - GlobalPOWER Roll 1, 2006 (Box 204)
  - GlobalPOWER Rolls 2-9, 2006 (Box 205)
  - GlobalPOWER Rolls 10-12, 2006 (Box 206)
  - AK LEG Ex & Untitled Photo Set, March 8. 2006-November 19, 2006 (Box 206)
  - FPI, September 7, 2006 (Box 206)
  - GlobalPOWER Photos for News, 2007 (Box 206)
  - GlobalPOWER, 2007-2008 (Box 207)
  - FPI, 2009 (Box 207)
  - GP, 2009 (Box 207)
  - For GP E News and Website Collage, 2010 (Box 207)
  - UN AIDS Reception, March 30, 2010 (Box 207)
  - For GP Africa ENEWS and Website + to send to UNAIDS General, October 29, 2010 (Box 207)
  - CWPS Post Election Action Convening, 2012 (Box 207)
  - GlobalPOWER Africa, 2012 (Box 207)
  - Lunch (Box 207)
  - WW & untitled, 1993 (Box 207)
  - Fatherhood Symposium (Box 208)
  - Suggested News Pics (Box 208)
  - Suggested News Pics & NCSL, 2004 (Box 208)
  - FPI & GP, 2006 (Box 208)
  - Untitled (Box 208-210)
  - Emails and Assorted Photographs, 2012 (Box 210)
  - Assorted Black & White Photographs, Negatives, Card (Box 210)
  - Women as Healers Tapes (Box 211-221)